Aarón Ojeda Reyes

aaron.ojeda.reyes@gmail.com www.linkedin.com/in/aaojeda +34 670 69 22 26

Self-motivated, analytical and creative software engineer. One way or another, I have been linked to video games professionally, personally or academically during my whole life. Needless to say, I love them. My thesis was about 2D platformers development with C++ and SDL. Leaving aside video games, I have experience in data science and a strong knowledge on basketball.

Languages	C++ (Main). Knowledge on C#, Python, Java, C, Assemblers
Libraries	SDL, Qt, TinyXML
Tools	Unity, GameMaker Studio, MIT App Inventor, Tiled
Interests	Video game development, Data Science, Basketball

KEY ACHIEVEMENTS

BoomBox S.L.U. Nov 2017 - Feb 2018. Unity Developer

Mobile video game development using Unity engine.

Computer Science Thesis. 2015 - 2017

• Game engine and GUI for the development of 2D platform games (C++).

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

BoomBox S.L.U. Nov 2017 - Feb 2018. Unity Developer

- Part of the team that developed American Girl World and Hemp Inc, two commercial mobile games for Android and iOS.
- In charge of the localization of both games.

BizKidz Lab. Oct 2014 - Nov 2015. Teacher

 Teaching children in whorkshops and out-of-school activities about designing and programming video games and Android Apps using GameMaker Studio and MIT App Inventor.

e-pione. Sept 2013 - Aug 2014. Co-founder, Data Scientist & Software Engineer

 Designing and developing an intelligent classification system based on machine learning algorithms.

- Cleaning and preprocessing different datasets.
- Meeting with neurologist and neuropsychologist for requirement analysis.

Freelance. Mar 2014 - Jun 2014. Data Scientist & Software Engineer

• Design and development of a prediction software to forecast exchange rates.

EDUCATION BACKGROUND

2006-2017 Computer Science Engineer's Degree (5 years). Thesis about 2D platformers development (distinction with honors). University of Las Palmas de Gran Canaria, Las Palmas, Spain.

2010-2011 Erasmus Exchange to Politechnika Krakowska (PK), Krakow, Poland.

2011-2012 Sicue Exchange to Universidad de Granada, Granada, Spain.

OWN PROJECTS

S2PEditor (*Thesis*) Game engine and GUI for the development of 2D platform games in Windows. Built using C++, SDL and Qt.

Check it on https://github.com/afrosistema/S2PEditor

LANGUAGES

Spanish Mother tongue

English Fluent spoken and written - B2

ADDITIONAL INFORMATION

Driving license B